Titouan Renard,

Master student in Robotics with a minor in Data Science

© (+41) 79 944 61 65

図 titouan.renard@epfl.ch 命 github.com/RenardDesNeiges

© Rue de la paix 9, 1020 Renens, Switzerland

I am student at EPFL currently pursuing a Master of Sciences in Robotics with a minor in Data Science. I am interested in control theory, machine learning and their applications to robotic systems. I also have some experience in student associations and am proficient in French and English.

Education

	Ongoing Master in Robotics with a Minor in Data Science , Lausanne, Switzerland EPFL, STI and IC faculties	2020-Present
	Bachelor in Microengineering , Lausanne, Switzerland EPFL, STI faculty	2020
	Bilingual Maturité , Neuchâtel, Switzerland French-English bilingual high-school, Lycée Denis de Rougemont, Physics and Applied Math	2016
Experience		
	Student-Assistant at EPFL , for the courses "Physique Générale 1" (Newtonian Mechanics), "Microinformatique" (basics of embedded systems programming for Microengineering students) and Material Sciences Practicals	2018-Present
	Responsable Politique , member of the direction comity of Unipoly (student's association for sustainabily at EPFL), responsible for interactions with stakeholders and EPFL's direction on matters of sustainabily on campus. Public relations experience, some experience with media and press releases.	2020-2021
	Responsible of Events for the 2020 sustainabily week on EPFL campus, Unipoly, Management and coordination of about 30 events on EPFL and UNIL's campuses.	2020

implementation of a simple vision-based localization system using C++ and OpenCV. **European Youth Parliament**, Switzerland

2015-2016

2018

English language public speaking experience.

Skills

Programming, in C, C++, Javascript, Matlab, Python and Scala

Math and Applied Math, Probabilities, Linear Algebra, Calculus, Dynamic System Theory and Control Theory, Signal Processing, Algorithmic Design and Analysis

Summer Internship, Birorobotics Lab EPFL, at the Biorobotics Laboratory at EPFL,

Languages, French (native proficiency), English (full proficiency), German (high-school level, B2)

Soft Skills, public speaking, writing and team management learned in the context student associations

Relevant Courses

Course	Grade
Model Predictive Control (ME-425)	5.75/6
Algorithms (CS-250)	5.5/6
Advanced Algorithms (CS-450)	6/6
Artifical Neural Networks (CS-456)	5.75/6
Aerial Robotics (MICRO-502)	5/6
Computer Vision (CS-442)	5.5/6
Distributed Intelligent Systems (ENG-466)	5/6